{
    "subject": "resource/Savyon_Liebrecht",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthYear",
    "object": "1948",
    "human_readable": "Savyon Liebrecht was born in 1948.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9273836612701416,
            "question": "In what year was Savyon Liebrecht born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8656530976295471,
            "question": "Was Savyon Liebrecht born before or after 1950?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8209497332572937,
            "question": "What year marks Savyon Liebrecht's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7978460788726807,
            "question": "What is Savyon Liebrecht's birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7588841915130615,
            "question": "What decade was Savyon Liebrecht born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7359727025032043,
            "question": "Is Savyon Liebrecht older than someone born in 1950?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6124832630157471,
            "question": "How old is Savyon Liebrecht?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5873718857765198,
            "question": "Does Savyon Liebrecht's birth year fall within the 20th century?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47566670179367065,
            "question": "When did Savyon Liebrecht come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26041093468666077,
            "question": "If today is October 26, 2023, how many years has Savyon Liebrecht lived?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Savyon Liebrecht was born in 1948.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2321_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Savyon Liebrecht come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2321_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Savyon Liebrecht's birth year fall within the 20th century?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2321_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old is Savyon Liebrecht?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2321_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2321_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2321_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2321_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2321_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2321_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2321_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2321_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2321_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2321_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2321_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all the documents (except one) mention Savyon Liebrecht's birth year as 1948, with some providing more context and details about her life."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents, which consistently state that Savyon Liebrecht was born in 1948."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}